http://www.heli-ski.com/privacy

Our Commitment To Privacy
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on every page of our website and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.
The Information We Collect: This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the North Cascade Heli website. On some pages, you can send us your email address. The types of personal information collected on this page is:
Name
Email address
Phone number
And any other info put into the message field
The Way We Use Information:
We use the information you provide about yourself to contact you based on your request for additional information. We do not share this information with outside parties.
We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. You can register with our website if you would like to receive our email news letter as well as updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you use the box to submit your email.
We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.
Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.
Our Commitment To Data Security:
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information:
You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. If you call us, we can lookup the information we have about you.
To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.
How To Contact Us:
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at 509-9963272 or send us an email at info@heli-ski.com
Footer 6
Ski Trips
Heli Ski
Backcountry Touring
Yurt
Footer 1
PLAN Your TRIP
Accommodations
Stay Connected
Sign up for the North Cascade Heli newsletter.
Sign up now
The "Access" in Backcountry Access means a lot more than just getting after it in the mountains. Since 1994, our avalanche safety gear has been designed to make backcountry riding and snow safety more accessible: more widely available, affordable and easy-to-use. The "A" in access also stands for access for all backcountry users, no matter what the means of travel. Our discretionary spending goes into promoting avalanche education, not restricting access to the backcountry. Great products, great value, and a balanced perspective: that's how BCA has become the most trusted name in backcountry safety.
Website
Blue Star Coffee Roasters is located in Twisp, Washington. We are a wholesale provider of world-class, hand-roasted coffee to the Methow Valley and beyond. Voted one of the top three micro roasters in North America by Roast Magazine in 2017, and winner of America’s Best Espresso at Seattle Coffee Fest in 2012, we bring over twenty-five years of award-winning coffee experience to the region.
Website
Located just 15 miles west of Winthrop in Mazama, Washington, the Freestone Inn offers a quiet setting and casual atmosphere. Our 36 units either have a lake or forest view, private veranda or deck and fireplace.
Website
Heli-Ski U.S. Association, Inc. is a Utah nonprofit corporation whose members represent the very best helicopter skiing operators in the United States. Our members work cooperatively to help establish the highest safety and operating standards in the helicopter skiing industry. However, each member is an independent corporation, solely responsible to its customers and employees.
Website
From our home in Norway, Helly Hansen has been making professional grade gear to help people stay and feel alive for almost 140 years. It all started in 1877 when sea captain Helly Juell Hansen found a better way to stay protected from the harsh Norwegian elements. Soon thereafter, Captain Hansen and his wife Margrethe launched a business producing waterproof oilskin jackets, trousers, sou’westers and tarpaulins made from coarse linen soaked in linseed oil – and the legend was born!
Website
Morez in the valley of the French eyewear industry, a Jura native launched a brand which would not yet be called Julbo, but almost… thanks to the name of its founder, Jules Baud. He started his business designing optical eyewear with one idea in mind: innovation. in the early 20th century, at the request of Chamonix crystal hunters wanting to protect their eyes in the mountains, he designed the first «Cristalliers» sunglasses, marking the start of Julbo’s optical sun protection story.
Website
K2 Skis has been seeking fun through innovation since 1962. Our all-mountain philosophy and technological advancements continue to lead the ski industry.
Website
K2 Snowboarding has supported riders globally for over 25 years with authentic, innovative snowboards, boots, and bindings to create epic days in the snow.
Website
Alpine winter sports as we know them today were still very much in their infancy some 50 years ago. Sports journalist and ski instructor Hannes Marker, concerned by injuries suffered by his eager students and other inexperienced skiers on the slopes of the Bavarian Alps, resolved to lessen the sport’s inherent risks. And in so doing, he founded the company MARKER. Marker determined that inadequately responsive skiing equipment represented the single biggest cause of injuries. His perfectionist, problem-solving approach and commitment to arduous work paid off.
Website
Precision is an aerospace company headquartered in McMinnville, Oregon. We have offered unmatched manned and unmanned operations for over three decades. We're a team of pilots, gearheads, veterans and logistics experts who bring reliability to every expedition. From heliskiing in the PNW, to unmanned surveillance overseas, we're voyagers of all things airborne in any environment.
Website
North Cascade Heli, Inc. is an equal opportunity provider and operates under special use permit with the Okanogan Wenatchee National Forest.
Website
© North Cascade Heli. All Rights Reserved. Legal | Privacy Policy
Designed & Developed by 3Sherpas
